https://www.happinessiscamping.org/privacy-policy-2/

Overview
This privacy policy will advise you about our guidelines concerning the use of your personal information, including, without limitation, the reasonable efforts we make to protect your personal information in accordance with these guidelines, and about what choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this policy carefully. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our Site. We will post those changes here so that you will always know our policies regarding what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this policy regularly.
We keep your private information private by:
Not selling your information—You’ve entrusted us with your personal information, and we’re committed to using it wisely. Happiness Is Camping will not sell your personal information to anyone, for any reason, at any time.
Restricting who has access to your information—We take precautions to ensure that your internet account and personal information are accessible only by employees who are authorized to have access to your personal information.
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at:
Happiness Is Camping
62 Sunset Lake Road
Hardwick, NJ 07825
908-362-6733
Scope of Privacy Policy
This policy applies to your use of this site. This policy does not apply to your use of unaffiliated sites to which this site only links.
Personal Identification Information
We may request personal identification information from you (such as your last name, age, city and state) in connection with your use of, or participation in registration for surveys, forums, content submissions, chats, bulletin boards, discussion groups, requests for suggestions, or additional information, and in connection with other activities, services or resources we make available on any of our Sites. In all of these cases, we will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Except as otherwise provided in this policy, we reasonably endeavor to ensure that we never intentionally disclose any personal identification information about you as an individual user to any third party without having received your permission (through opt-in or similar procedures) except as provided for herein or otherwise as permitted or required under law. Further, Happiness Is Camping may contact you based on the information you provide online whether in connection with your registration or in such places as the above described forums.
If you do provide us with personal information for any of these activities, we may use it to conduct the activity.
Happiness Is Camping does not rent or sell personal identification information, including information provided by children, to outside marketers. In certain circumstances, Happiness Is Camping may share personal identification information with trusted service providers that need access to your information to provide operational or other support services or we may share this aggregate statistical information with other third parties; to ensure the confidentiality and security of this information, service providers must agree to safeguard all information in strict compliance with our policy. We may also provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it.
Non-Personal Identification Information
We collect non-personal identification information without limitation, through the use of the following types of methodology:
“Cookie” technology: A “cookie” is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system.
“IP address tracking”: An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are on the Internet. When you request pages from our Sites, our servers log your IP address.
“Web beacons”: A Web beacon, or “clear gif,” is a small graphic image on a webpage or web-based document that a website can use to determine information about a user.
Non-personal identification information might include the browser you use, the type of computer, technical information about your means of connection to our Sites (such as the operating systems and the Internet service providers utilized), and other similar information. Our systems may also automatically gather information about the areas you visit and search terms you utilize on our Sites and about the links you may select from within our Sites to other areas of the World Wide Web or elsewhere online.
We use such information for our business purposes, and, in particular, primarily to administer the Sites, and, in the aggregate, to what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our Sites.
Privacy of Children
We are mindful that young people need special safeguards and privacy protection. We realize that they may not understand all the provisions of our policy or be able to make thoughtful decisions about the choices that are made available to our adult users. We strongly urge all parents to participate in their children’s exploration of the Internet and any online services, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online.
Donations
We collect only enough information to process your donation and do not use the information for any other purpose. Your payment information is transmitted to us using a secure internet method that helps ensure the privacy of this information. During the time your payment information resides on our computers, it is in an encrypted format and can only be accessed by authorized personnel with a decryption key.
Links to Other Sites
Users will find other content on our Sites that link to the sites and services of other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policy (policies) at all. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.
Choice/Opt-Out
If you “opt-in” to receive information from us, you can change your mind later. If at any time you would like to stop receiving such information or opt-out of a feature, you may change your options by contacting us at 908-362-6733. You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our databases and servers, although we will always make reasonable efforts to do so upon your request, and we are unable to have your information removed from the records of any third party who has been provided with your information in accordance with this policy.
Consent to Transfer
The Sites are operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Website, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using any of the Sites, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy, your promise to comply with the representations you make and contained in the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions, and your understanding of the scope and limitations of the protections provided under the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to these policies, please do not use our Sites. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.
Upcoming Events
Dec
27
Sun
Virtual Holiday Camp
Dec 27 – Dec 30 all-day
Virtual Holiday Camp
Dec 27 – Dec 30 all-day
We are proud to offer our first ever session of Virtual Holiday Camp! VHC will be an extension of Virtual Camp. Campers will log into Zoom each evening at 7:00 and participate in unique virtual activities. Come join us for camp favorites and even a Color War event! Fill out[...]
May
28
Fri
Family Camp
May 28 – May 31 all-day
Family Camp
May 28 – May 31 all-day
Family Camp is available for children with cancer, ages 6-16, who have never attended Happiness Is Camping and their immediate family members. Family Camp is completely FREE for all attendees. Climb our ropes course which includes a giant swing, zipline, flying squirrel, climbing tower, and so much more. Swim in[...]
Jun
1
Tue
40th Anniversary Reunion!
Jun 1 – Aug 31 all-day
40th Anniversary Reunion!
Jun 1 – Aug 31 all-day
We are incredibly excited to host our 40th Anniversary Reunion! The exact date is still TBD but will take place in Summer 2021. Camp staff and Alumni Board Chairs Cody Hennelly, Maureen Hussey, and Charlie Callari are hard at work scheduling the day’s events. We look forward to hosting classic[...]
View Calendar
What’s New
Summer Camp 2021 PlanCheck Out Our New Limited Edition Merchandise Line!COVID-19 Update
